Well done, well done.
You've reached the end of functions and this is a really important module.
This is where we've learned to create these little, these little boxes that encapsulate code.
Code that can be used over and over again.
So as we said functions there are lots of different types of functions.
And they fit into categories broader categories called modules.
And so you can have modules that have to do with math functions as we've seen, or modules that have
to do with graphic functions, modules that handle manipulation of lists, etc., all different types
of functions.
And not only did we look at them, we looked at how you can use them and you've been using them the
whole time, whether you knew it or not.
Simple functions like print, but when you're using them, or more exciting functions like random,
which we want to use in our game that we're going to create shortly, those functions always require
you to pass parameters.
Very important that you pass the correct number of parameters in order to call the function.
And then the function will return something.
That's the whole reason they're there.
They're not just a black box that does nothing.
They normally return a value and we can work with that value.
And so we moved on and showed you how you could create your own function.
We created a function that looked at the days of the week and whether something was a weekend.
And what was exciting about that is you could use that function to test if a certain day of the week
was the weekend or not.
So functions are a very powerful, and they are something that you're going to use increasingly.
So they're not difficult to use.
It's all about you're putting your code into these little packages.
And then once they're packaged and tested, you know that you can continue to easily use it all over
your program.
So these are very good habits that you need to develop.
And we've looked at a couple of them.
We've looked at layout how you must keep your indentation proper.
We've looked at including comments.
And another very important one is keeping the cohesiveness of your modules and of your coding by putting
together functions.
So well done.
You've reached the end of this module and you are now ready for some really exciting action in the next
section.